[
{"question":"1. Soil water content is expressed on what basis ",
"answers":{
            "a":"Gravimetric ",
            "b":"volumetric",
            "c":"Both a and b",
            "d":"None"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"2. Water content affects",
"answers":{
            "a":"Strength and settlement of soils",
            "b":"Sensitivity",
            "c":"Relative dendity",
            "d":"Relative dendity"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"}, 

{"question":"3. The water content of clays are generally ________ sand and silts  ",
"answers":{
            "a":"Greater than",
            "b":"Equal to",
            "c":"Less than",
            "d":"None"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"4. The standard method of determining water content is",
"answers":{
            "a":"Oven-drying method",
            "b":"Calcium carbide method",
            "c":"Alcohol method",
            "d":"Pycnometer method"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"}, 

{"question":"5. Water content for dry soil is equal to ",
"answers":{
            "a":"0 ",
            "b":"<0",
            "c":">0",
            "d":"<=0"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"6. Pycnometer is used to determined",
"answers":{
            "a":"Water content and void ratio",
            "b":"Specific gravity and dry density",
            "c":"Water content and specific gravity",
            "d":"Void ratio and dry density"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"}, 

{"question":"7. The water content of soil is defined as the ratio of",
"answers":{
            "a":"Volume of water to volume of given soil",
            "b":"Volume of water to volume of voids in soil",
            "c":"Weight of water to weight of air voids",
            "d":"Weight of water to weight of solids of given mass of soil"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"8. Water content of a soil sample is the difference of weight of given sample at the temperature and the weight determined after drying it for 24hrs at temperature ranging from ⁰c ",
"answers":{
            "a":"80⁰ c to 90⁰c",
            "b":"90⁰c to 95⁰c ",
            "c":"95⁰c to 100⁰c",
            "d":"105⁰c to 110⁰c"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"}, 


w{"question":"9. Water content for saturation soil is ",
"answers":{
            "a":"=0",
            "b":"<0",
            "c":">0",
            "d":"<=0"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"10. The ratio of the weight of given volume of soil solids to the weight of an equal of distilled water at the given temperature, is known",
"answers":{
            "a":"Porosity",
            "b":"Specific gravity",
            "c":"Void ratio",
            "d":"Water content"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"}

]
